哈罗
Hello!
这是什么
What's this?
对了  是那个女生的电话
Oh, right! It's that girl's phone number.
在这里  只是一个电话号码
There it is. Just a phone number...
一个超辣的女生给我的
a really hot girl gave me.
也没什么  只是她家的电话...
It's no big deal. I mean, it is her home phone number, but...
差点就掉了
Almost lost this baby!
可爱的亚曼达把电话给我  我却掉了
The lovely Amanda gives me her number, and I go and drop it.
谢谢
Thank you.
《老友记》  第四季  第05集  乔伊的新女友
Friends S04E05  The one with Joey's new girlfriend
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
瑞秋  嗯
Rachel? Yeah?
你的生日是几号  5月5号  做什么
When's your birthday? May fifth, why?
我只是在记大家的生日
I'm just making a list of people's birthdays.
我是12月... 随便
Mine's December... Yeah, whatever.
她真漂亮
She's pretty!
好漂亮  真...好...真漂亮
Pretty, pretty girl. The pretty...She's pretty.
去约她嘛
Go ask her out.
有什么大不了的  我搞不好会死
What's the worst that could happen? I could die.
一个人的确很难熬
Yeah, it's tough being single.
所以我很高兴  我认识了亚曼达
That's why I'm so glad I found Amanda.
罗斯  你们只出去过一次
Ross, you guys went out once.
你们带小孩去游乐城  你连亲都没亲她
You took your kids to Chuck E. Cheese, and you didn't even kiss her.
我会泄露秘密
I tell people secrets.
好让别人喜欢我
It makes them like me.
菲比
Phoebe.
你生病了  别唱了  回家上床休息吧
You're sick, you shouldn't play. You should just go home, get in bed, and stay there.
但是我失业了
But I'm unemployed.
只剩下音乐
my music is all I really have now.
音乐和自己做鞋子  很美吧
Well music, and making my own shoes. Pretty, huh?
好  我去
All right, I'm gonna do it.
我去搞定她
I'm gonna go get shot down.
有什么建议
Any advice?
展现你的本色
Just be yourself...
但别过火
but not too much.
祝我好运
Wish me luck.
加油
Good luck!
心里念就行了
Wish it!
你好  我坐在那里...
Hi, I was just sitting over there and...
钱德  我是钱德  我有说吗
Chandler. My name is Chandler. Did I say that?
没有  你好  我是凯西
No, you didn't. Hi, I'm Kathy.
凯西是哪个  K还是C  是K
Kathy with a K or a C? With a K.
你还真会搭讪
You are really good at this!
别这么说  我会很尴尬的
Hey, come on, give me a break, I'm out on a limb here.
你说得对  我道歉
I'm sorry, you're right, I apologize.
但是  我跟别人有约
But I should tell you, I'm waiting for a date.
他来了
And there he is now!
你们已经认识了
I see you guys already met.
是啊  我正在示范
Yes-yes, I was just trying to figure out a way to...
如何把我那很大的脚
demonstrate how I could get my exceptionally large feet...
塞进我那更大的嘴里
into my even bigger mouth.
我没有对你说过吗
Didrt I tell you?
他最爱表现了
Always showing off.
首先我要说  我感冒了
Before I start, I just wanna say that, I have a cold.
要是我唱到一半打喷嚏  不是故意的啊
So if I sneeze in the middle of song, it's not on purpose.
除了"胡椒人"的最后一句
Except the last verse of "Pepper People."
臭臭猫  臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat
他们喂你吃什么
What are they feeding you?
这声音不赖
This chick sounds good.
臭臭猫
Smelly cat
甘德  乖  拿杯威士忌来
Hey Gunther, be a good little boy and bring me a whiskey.
想不到半夜2点半  还要抢遥控器
Jeez, at 2:30 in the morning, I didn't expect to have to fight over the remote.
对不起  我想看厄尼柯瓦克斯的重播
I'm sorry, it's just this Ernie Cofax thing on in a few minutes I wanted to watch.
我也要看那个
Oh my God! That's why I got up too!
不会吧  我爱死他了
You're kidding? I love him!
下午很抱歉  要是知道你们...我也不会
Hey, listen, I'm sorry about this afternoon, if I would've known you guys were...I never would've...
道什么歉
Oh, please.
乔伊说  你们是在表演课认识的
So, Joey tells me you two met in acting class.
对  我们两个一组  乔伊选了三场戏
Yeah, they teamed us up as partners. Joey picked three scenes for us to do.
都是亲热戏
all of them had us making out.
太好了  他原先都是逼着我跟他练
That's a good thing actually, because ah, he used to have me rehearse with him.
开始了吗  还没  但是这个伸缩扫把很棒
Is it on? No, but this Wonder Broom is amazing!
就是它
Oh, my God!
开始了
It's on!
小不点  过来
Here we go, little fella.
那鸭子呢
What about the duck?
鸭子会游泳
The duck can swim.
烂泥巴鞋
My sticky shoes
沾满烂泥巴的鞋
My sticky, sticky shoes
你为什么揪着我不放
Why you stick on me?
宝贝
Baby
谢谢你的灯光
Thanks for the lights, honey.
太精彩了
Way to go!
你的声音好有磁性
Your cold makes you sound great.
好好玩  我真是太性感了
It's fun. God, I love how sexy I am!
凯西  该走了  我们要去买仓鼠
Kath, we should get going. We're going to buy hamsters.
我喜欢仓鼠
I love them.
不是那样的  我在替一个医疗研究员工作
No, it's not like that. I work for a medical researcher.
去玩吧  好
Well, have fun. Okay.
总算医学界也在救助生病的仓鼠了
Well, I think it's great that the medical community is finally trying to help sick hamsters.
知道吗  我喜欢凯西  对啊
You know what? I like Kathy. Yeah.
我也是  她好酷好漂亮
Yeah! me too! She's so cool and pretty.
是啊
She is.
她既聪明又风趣
She's smart and funny.
我们昨晚聊了一整夜  她聊到一些...
you know? We were up all last night talking, she said the funniest thing about...
怎样
What?
你爱她
You love her.
我没有
No, I don't.
你有  钱德爱凯西
Yes, you do. Chandler loves Kathy.
菲比  饶了他吧  谢了  罗斯
Come on, Pheebs just lay off him. Thank you. Ross.
现在他有点敏感  因为他恋爱了
Yeah, he's a little sensitive right now, because he's so in love.
好吧
All right.
凯西  我爱你
Kathy, I love you!
我得写一些悲情的歌来配合我的新哭腔
So, I need to write some depressing stuff to go along with my new floozy voice
但我没有悲惨的遭遇
but nothing that sad has ever really happened to me.
你妈自杀的事呢
How about your mom dying?
或是你14岁时流落街头
Or having to live on the streets when you were 14?
我可以写头发翘起来那次
I could write about the time my hair did that "Woo-hoo" thing.
我晚上要去亚曼达家
So I'm going over to Amanda's tonight!
瑞秋不在
Rachel's not here.
你跟她进展如何
How's it going with her?
很棒  搞不好今晚就有机会
Great, actually. I'm thinking tonight may be the night.
两个孩子会一起玩  等他们睡了
I mean, the kids are gonna play together and then when they're asleep...
亚曼达和我再开一瓶酒
I'm thinking Amanda and I break open a bottle of wine...
我们自己来玩
do a little playing ourselves.
嗨  这是贾许
Hi, guys! This is Josh.
贾许  她们是我的朋友
Josh, these are my friends.
那是罗斯
And that's Ross.
贾许  你好
Hi, Josh.
兄弟们
Dudes.
你打过校队
So, did you play in college?
现在还是  明年我想进大学
I still do. Next year, I hope to make varsity.
罗斯  你高中不是踢过足球
Ross, didn't you ah, play soccer in High School?
不对  你只是用电脑帮他们排赛程表
No, wait. that's right. You just organized their game schedules on your Commodore 64.
不早了  我还有球赛  我先闪了
Well, it's getting late, I've got to get to the game, so I'm gonna...head
我会想你的
I'll miss you.
爽
Dope!
哇  很可爱嘛
Wow! Cute one.
非常可爱  我知道  他很棒吧
Very cute. I know. Isn't he great?
总算来了一段有趣的恋情
So nice to finally be in a fun relationship, you know?
他相当有趣
There's nothing boring about him.
我敢赌他一定没进过博物馆
and, I bet he's never set foot in a museum.
也许他快有机会了
Well maybe he'll get to go soon
像校外教学什么的
Like on a class trip or something.
你们知道  他还有哪里好
You know what else is great about him?
该怎么形容呢
what is the word for the adult...
房间里没有恐龙玩具的男人
that doesn't have dinosaur toys in their bedroom?
什么意思
What was that?
莫妮卡知道
Monica knows.
那是罗斯发明来吓爸妈的
It's this dumb thing that Ross made up to try to fool our parents.
其实就是比中指的意思
It's a way of giving the finger without actually having to give it.
你发明这个手势  让我哭了
I remember I cried the night you made it up.
我第一次明白  我比我哥酷
because it was the first time that I realized that I was actually cooler than my older brother.
我要去准备...
Well, I'm gonna go get ready...
今晚的赴约了
for my date tonight...
我热血沸腾
so I'll just "head."
我也该走了  1小时后要上台
Yeah, I should go too. because I'm playing in one hour.
你们应该来听
You guys should come hear me.
来听听
Hear me.
烂泥巴鞋...
My sticky shoes
我的性感破锣嗓子没了
I lost my sexy phlegm!
嗨  班
Hi, Ben.
你好性感  谢谢
You look great! Thanks.
嗨  汤米
Hey, Tommy!
我好高兴你今晚能来
I am so glad that you could come over tonight.
不  这是我的荣幸
Oh, no. It's my pleasure.
我的手机号码在餐台上
Okay, well, my cell phone number is right here on the counter.
冰箱里的东西自己拿
Please, help yourself to anything in the fridge.
真的很谢谢你  我想约这个男的想了好久
I appreciate this so much. I have been trying to go out with...
有一个月了
this guy for like a month.
本来不想说  但我希望你等孩子睡了
I don't mean to be a square, but I'd really appreciate it if you wait and drink your wine...
再喝你的红酒
after the kids are asleep.
谢谢你  希望改天我也能帮你
Thanks for this. I hope I can do the same for you sometime.
谁想打长途
Who wants to make some long-distance calls?
凯西  凯西  喂
Kathy! Kathy! Hi!
凯西  凯西
Kathy! Kathy!
凯西
Kathy!
让开  让开
Fetch! Fetch it!
凯西  凯西
Kathy! Kathy!
凯西
Kathy!
钱德  你怎么在这里
Chandler, what are you doing here?
我只是来打个招呼
I just wanted to say, "Hey!"
嘿
Hey.
好
Okay.
不是吧  你说得太严重了吧
Oh, You're making it sound worse than it actually was.
她的男伴给了我10块钱
Her date tipped me $10
菲比  你干什么
Pheebs, what are you doing?
我想恢复性感  所以我想感冒
Okay, I wanna be sexy again so I'm trying to catch a cold.
应该很容易  感冒很常见
Should be easy. They're pretty common.
菲比  你会得肺炎的
Phoebe, You'll catch pneumonia!
说得对  我爱上了乔伊的女朋友
Okay, you were right. I'm in love with Joey's girlfriend.
什么  真的吗
What? Are you serious?
怎么可能  你们根本不熟
How is that possible? You barely know her.
我不知道  我就是...
I don't know. I just...
无法忘记她
I can't get her out of my head.
我很糟糕  非常非常的糟
I'm a very bad person. I'm a very, very bad person.
我是个烂人
I'm a horrible person.
"才不是呢  我们还是爱你"
"No you're not Chandler! We still love you Chandler!"
菲比  我染上你的感冒了
Oh gosh, Phoebe, I think I caught your cold.
是偷走才对
You mean you stole it!
打喷嚏不要捂嘴巴
Don't cover your mouth when you do that!
我们正在说你
We were just talking about you.
真的
Really?
对  就是你喝醉睡着那次
Yeah-yeah, I told her about the time you got drunk and fell asleep...
头泡在马桶里
with your head in the toilet.
泡得刚刚好
Right in there!
九十九
Ninety-nine...
一百  好了没  我来了
a hundred. Ready or not, here I come!
好吧  我再解释一次规则
All right, let's go over the concept one more time.
伙计  晚上要不要跟我和凯西吃饭
Hey guys.  Listen, you wanna get some dinner with me and Kathy tonight?
我已经吃饱了
You know what? I already ate.
才4点半
It's 4:30.
我星期一吃得很饱
You know I had a big meal on Monday.
可以撑一个礼拜
So that's just gonna get me straight through the week.
我知道是怎么回事
Okay, I see what's going on here.
你知道  对
You do? Yeah.
你不喜欢凯西
You don't like Kathy.
被你猜对了
You got me.
我们交往至今  你一直在躲她
Yeah, you've been avoiding her ever since we started going out.
我曾经努力想去喜欢珍妮丝
Look, I made an effort to like Janice,
现在该你去试着喜欢凯西  陪我们去吃饭了  好吗
now I think it's your turn to make an effort to like Kathy by going out to dinner with us. Right?
对  没错  很好  而且我请客
Yeah, right. Good. And hey, my treat.
不过你不想吃  对吧  对
But that's only because you're not eating anything, right? Right.
罗斯不在
Ross isn't here.
放手
Stop it!
派对上见
So I'll see you at the party?
啤酒免费喝到饱  24  7
Beer's beer man, 24, 7!
我一定会嫁给他
I am so gonna marry that guy.
怎么了
What?
我觉得他偷我的钱  为什么
I think he's stealing from me. Why?
因为他真的偷我的钱
Because he's stealing from me!
是我
Hi, it's me...
还有热汤
and soup.
贾许穿你的皮衣  看起来好帅
I just saw Josh. He looked so yummy in your leather jacket.
来  我不吃鸡  所以只有汤
Here, now I don't eat chicken, so it's just noodle soup.
熬汤时又没放鸡  跟水没什么两样
And there's no chicken in the broth either, so it's really just... noodle water.
谢谢你菲比  当然
Thank you so much Phoebe. Sure.
你拿那个干嘛
What are you doing with those?!
要你的病菌  我想再感冒
But, I need your germs! I want my cold back!
我怀念我的性感嗓音
I miss my sexy voice.
菲比  对不起
Sorry, Phoebe.
没关系
It's okay.
汤好喝吗
How's the soup?
天呀  那个女生的内衣都露出来了
God, guys, check it out, you can see that girl's underwear!
很棒吧
Is she great, or what?
你觉得她如何
So? Huh? What do you think?
她不是我的型
She's not really my type.
不是你的型  大美女啊
Not your type? She's gorgeous.
知道吗  因为她穿网袜
You know what I think it is? It's the fishnet stockings.
看到女生穿网袜  我就想到...
Whenever I see a girl in fishnet stockings it reminds me of...
我爸穿网袜的样子
my father in fishnet stockings.
我有点了解  你为何单身了
Okay. Understanding a little more why you're single.
我有个很漂亮的朋友  可以一起约会
I have a friend you would like, she's really pretty. And then we could double date!
不必了
No, thanks.
我也有几个丑朋友   没有对象
Okay, I've got some ugly friends, and they're all available too.
我去叫酒
Listen, I-I'm gonna grab a beer.
马上回来
I'll be right back.
你什么意思  什么
What was that? What?
凯西在示好  你却掉头就走
Kathy was being really nice and you just walked away. I thought we had a deal.
你要我怎样
Hey, look, what do you want from me?
我要你喜欢她
I want you to like her.
要是太难了  你起码可以装一下
But if that's too damned difficult for you, then the least you can do is pretend.
我正在装啊  再像一点
I am pretending. Then do it better.
不如我过去说  很喜欢她
Okay, what do you saw I go over there and say how much I like her?
不  我可以说我一直在想她
No-no it'll be good, I can tell her much I've been thinking about her.
认识以后  我就一直想着她
That I haven't stopped thinking about her since the moment I met her.
我无可救药  简直想掐死自己
That I'm so fantastically, over-the-top, wanna-slit-my-own-throat...
每一天每一分每一秒都爱着她
in love with her, that for every minute of every hour of every day...
我都在怨恨  为何是你先认识她
I can't believe my own damn bad luck that you met her first!
很不错
That's pretty good.
但是别那么夸张
But you might want to tone it down a little.
是亚曼达载我来的
So Amanda just dropped me off.
我就喜欢她这一点
That's one of the things I love about her.
成年人可以开车
She's old enough to drive.
你晚上不去找爸妈了
So uhh, I guess you're not going to mom and dad's tonight?
不了  对不起
No, sorry.
亚曼达呢
Well where's Amanda?
瑞秋  能帮我拿咳嗽药水
Hey Rach, could you get me some cough drops?
我在想你可以带她
I mean you know, I'm thinking. You could bring her...
去你的旧房间  然后不上床
and you guys could go up to your old room, and not make out.
罗斯  给我咳嗽药水
Ross, cough drops, please?
至少她跟我出去
At least I know she's not going out with me...
不是为了看限制级电影
to get into R-rated movies.
你干脆娶她算了
Why don't you just marry her?
我忘了  你不行  她不是同性恋
Oh no, wait a minute you can't, I'm sorry I forgot, she's not a lesbian.
亚曼达和我  什么都不是
You see Amanda and I have a very special... You have nothing!
你们根本没在约会  你是她的保姆
You're not even going out! You're her baby sitter!
你在做小女生做的事
You have a 12-year-old girl's job!
真可悲啊
That is so sad.
你笑什么  你男朋友还不是爱喝酒
And what are you laughing at, Miss My-keg-sucking-boyfriend...
又偷钱
is-stealing-from-me?
他偷了几块钱
So he stole a couple bucks from me. Big deal!
他买东西给我
At least he got me something with it.
那是我的
That's mine!
你们两个成熟一点好吗
Now, would you both please start acting like adults?
把咳嗽药水拿给我
And give me my cough drops!
好  对不起
Fine. Sorry.
拿去
Here.
谢谢
Thank you.
至少我还赚了10块钱
At least I made $ 10 in my relationship.
你知道
You know...?
游行的山羊在游行
Parading goats are parading
在大街上游行
Parading down the street
游行的山羊在游行
Parading goats are parading
留下小脚印
Leaving little treats
用这种声音唱  还能听吗
Does it even work without my sexy voice?
我喜欢
I like it.
甘德  亲我  什么
Gunther, kiss me. What?
副警长  快想办法
Do it, deputy! Do something!
我们没有要睡  你介意吗
Now, we're not actually gonna be sleeping in her, but do you mind?
我可以睡你的沙发吗
Can I sleep on your couch?
我还在等
And I'm still waiting
我的纸黏土人
For my papier-mache man
谢谢各位
Thank you, my babies.
瑞秋
Rachel?
我不知道你有没有听说  我和菲比的事
I don't know if you heard about what happened between me and Phoebe the other day?
没
No.
我们接吻了  不是我主动的  但我也没阻止
We kissed. I didn't initiate the kiss, but I also didn't stop it.
我一直觉得很内疚
and I've been feeling guilty.
好
Okay.
所以...
So...
我们没事吧
are we cool?
好
Okay.
我就知道你会谅解
I knew you'd understand.